Are you happy to be in Paris?
Oui.
>> Can you believe this?
>> Wow.
>> Oh my god.
>> No, Priscilla, this is worth it.
>> Bonjour, ma sœur princesse, et je suis
[music] à Paris pour la première fois.
>> [music]
>> We are headed to Paris. I am so excited.
The little girl in me is screaming. So,
of course, I had to bring you along.
[music] So, pack your bags and make sure
you have some really cute outfits. Let's
go to Paris.
>> Like, Priscilla, you have no idea. I've
been dreaming of this moment.
>> Aw, baby. You know this is on my
freaking vision board.
>> [laughter]
>> It's on my vision board.
>> It's been on my vision board since 2019.
>> [music]
>> I need to update you on the fact that
Bola missed this flight. So, you guys
know Bola lives in Houston
and I live in Dallas. We're like
star-crossed lovers.
I'm kidding. Her flight from Houston to
Istanbul I guess landed a little later.
So, by the time she landed, I called
her. She had just landed and they were
closing the gate and I was trying to
tell them like, "Please, my friend.
Like, my friend." This happens every
time we come to France. But, they just
put her on the next flight. So, I'm
going to just be waiting at the airport
for a while
and just like
waiting for my girl to get here.
So, I guess I'll just like, I don't
know, edit some videos. We'll talk to
you guys later. I'm about go through
immigration and grab my luggage and then
we will settle in and figure out what
we're going to do next.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So, I got the baggage.
Oh, somebody's going to eat me up for
that.
I got the baggage, all of our baggage,
but Fulani's baggage is not here.
So, I think her baggage is on the flight
that she's on right now, which
fingers crossed, God willing.
And there's a little bit of of a
surprise, which I'm not going to say. I
can't keep a secret from you. Oh my
gosh. Okay, basically Fulani and I are
going to another country
after Paris and then we're going to come
back to Paris after.
So, if you right now, as you're watching
right now, right now, right now, do not
cheat. Comment down below what country
you think it is or what city.
I want to see who knows me. Oh, this is
so exciting. Okay, I hope you are
enjoying the vlog so far. I know it
hasn't started,
but we'll be in more cities.
>> [laughter]
>> You look so beautiful the way you walked
up here.
I didn't even recognize you for a
second. Hi, my baby.
Oh, Fulani, you've been through so much.
>> [laughter]
>> You what? Um
Like like baggage
>> say anything.
I didn't ask them. They're like, "Do you
know she's
>> This is the worst airport, I tell you.
>> I don't know what to do with my life.
>> I don't know where
>> You guys know I am not one to focus
[music] on the negativity, but CDG
might be the worst airport I've ever
landed into. This airport is so
difficult to navigate, but that's okay.
We have our luggage, Fola has secured
her luggage, and we are now on the way
to our hotel.
Or so we thought. Really more like a
shoe box, but I don't want to get too
ahead of [music] myself.
Okay, we're on the way to the hotel.
We're going to yap yap yap a little bit,
and then we'll see you when we get
there.
>> Paris, the city of rats. I mean, love.
>> I'm glad I got that on camera.
>> [laughter]
>> What a beautiful hotel.
I wonder why the girl decided not to
stay here. But knowing how much Princess
tells us everything we're bound to find
out.
>> Oh,
>> WHAT THE HECK?
>> I GOT THE CAMERA.
WHY is it so small?
You can [music] see the first place was
a bust. Let's hope that the second
location is a lot more promising.
>> We just can't do a shoe box. I'm so
sorry.
>> So now we are going to an Airbnb, which
before [music] we were so anti-Airbnbs
cuz we just didn't want to do the
stairs.
But now [music] we'll do the stairs for
the space. It's a two-bedroom. Is it two
or three bedrooms?
>> Two.
>> It's a two-bedroom, two-bath. [music]
Ignore the first room for that. That was
just a teaser. We were just playing with
you, bro.
>> Yeah, we were just playing.
>> And we'll see you at the house.
>> Guys, I love this city,
and I haven't even been here for two
hours.
You know, you can just tell.
You can just tell.
I love it here.
We have seen a couple things that have
been a bit freaked out.
>> [music]
>> But, you know, Bullet just keeps saying,
"It's Paris."
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
Sweet.
>> [music]
>> Sweet.
No, I'm trying to count in in French.
>> [screaming]
>> Oh my gosh, it looks
>> Guys, welcome to our home, our little
apartment for the next few days.
It's so cute.
>> So cute.
>> I actually love it. We actually get all
the space we need.
>> And I love that they blocked the windows
so people can't
>> Me, too. They can't see.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, let's check out our rooms.
>> Door number one.
>> Okay.
>> [snorts]
[screaming]
>> Oh my gosh.
>> It's actually so cute.
>> So cute.
We're going to have to switch rooms
every day. It doesn't matter.
At least you can do your makeup here.
>> It's extra big.
>> Is it?
Oh, wow, you can actually unpack. That's
making me want to cry.
>> [laughter]
>> That hotel was actually so traumatizing.
>> Okay, door number two.
>> [laughter]
>> Aw, this is so cute.
>> Okay, so same layout.
>> It's literally the same thing, just
>> Cute mirror.
>> And light from the window.
>> And then I think this is the bathroom.
>> Yeah.
>> There's three doors.
>> Three doors.
>> Oh.
>> Is it a washer dryer?
>> Yeah.
>> [music]
>> Why is this a washer dryer?
Why is it like this?
This It literally is giving me
flashbacks to our Korea Airbnb.
>> It's really so cute.
>> It [music] still works. It's not like
Parisian, it's more modern.
Okay guys, I went ahead and unpacked
some of my stuff.
Um just so I can have it. It's so cute.
I love unpacking.
And then I laid out my dress for
tonight. I'm about to shower and get
ready. I'm actually so tired. I think
today has just been a bit of a draining
situation.
Having to like go get adapters and all
of these extra things that just weren't
going as planned
is making me so tired and sleepy. But we
do want to go out tonight. We want to at
least try just so we can kind of get a
feel for what to expect for the rest of
the week. Hello hello everybody.
The girls are ready.
Wait.
There we go.
Wait, let me get a coat.
>> Should I wear
that? Your brown one?
>> Yeah, I think you should wear that.
>> No, I think she would have worn that.
But I think this could be fun as a coat.
>> And I kind of want to try a new long
coat.
>> So you wanted to wear brown.
Oh my goodness. No way. This
is so funny. She said, "Yeah yeah, wear
the brown one." So Maureen, this dress
from Windsor
>> [music]
>> is literally just a simple black dress
in the words of Coco Chanel.
It's like 12:30 [music] right now. I
just want you to understand our original
itinerary
nowhere in the vicinity anymore.
Deleted. So now we're just on vibes and
I couldn't be happier, [music] truly.
Bye vlog.
There we go.
Got to lock the doors.
It'd be scary out here.
Yo, these doors are so heavy.
Jesus Christ. Olala.
Guys, it feels like we're the only
people on the street.
Where is everyone?
>> [laughter]
>> Why does Paris feel deserted?
Okay, we're getting in the Uber now. No,
literally, actually, where is everyone
on a Sunday night?
>> I think they're getting ready for work,
or something.
>> One thing about me, always order the
>> Oh, we just heard Olamide is performing
tonight. So, [music] you never know what
the night is going to bring. So, we need
to be all fed up, all hydrated, and
ready [music] to go.
We're going to be
out. We're going to be lit tonight.
>> Okay, well, me and Folla have a plan,
right? I hope you guys can hear us. The
plan
He's going to be like,
"Who are you?"
>> [laughter]
>> And we're going to be
>> We're going to act nonchalant.
>> Yeah, we're going to roll our eyes like,
"Whatever." Like, and then after a
while, I'll be like, "Okay, fine." And
then we'll come back.
>> [laughter]
>> And then we'll be
But then we're going to be sitting off
in the corner.
>> And then we're going to be like, 10
minutes. Like, remember like South of
France,
>> Yeah.
I know that he's not
going to be
our section.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Sing it now, y'all.
>> Baby [singing] boy, you stay on my mind.
Fulfill my fantasy.
>> Come on, girl. Tell me how you feel.
[music]
>> I think about [singing] you all the
time. I see you in my dreams.
>> You don't know the love I have for
>> Baby boy, my body
>> [singing]
>> goes wild. You rock my fantasy.
>> Come on, girl. Tell me what's the deal.
[music]
>> I think about you all the time. I see
you in my dreams.
>> You don't know the love I have
>> [music]
[music]
>> Huge. Wait, I got to go back.
Really? It's impossible to fit in the
frame. Okay, guys, we just finished our
um Omalay concert. That's what we're
calling it cuz that's really what it
was. Cuz we were
we were there like and I was like,
"Folorunsho, let's go see the Eiffel
Tower right now because I know that no
one will be here. Literally, there's no
one here but this one man who's on a
run.
And even he's in awe.
And I
This is Oh my god. Okay, wait, let's
turn so it's in the background.
Can you guys see it? Wait, wait, we got
to scoot up a little bit.
>> [gasps]
>> This is insane, guys.
>> Wow.
>> It's the Eiffel Tower WITH MY BABY.
I JUST
>> WOW. I'M
>> BELIEVE
>> SPEECHLESS. I'm so speechless.
>> It's huge. Everyone who says it's small
they're
>> I can't imagine it all lit up. I'll
probably cry when it's lit
>> up it is
gorgeous.
I just can't believe it's right in front
of us. I might cry actually.
>> I actually might cry.
I don't know why I'm getting emotional
cuz if I deep it I'm going to actually
get emotional about this.
>> I just think about like when I was
younger in Nigeria
the Eiffel Tower just felt like such a
outlandish thing like
I never thought in my wildest dreams
that I would actually be [music]
But that word in reality
>> Like we're literally just sitting here
looking at it.
It's so surreal.
Wait.
Oh,
you okay?
Are you crying?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, I'm so happy.
And it's not even lit up yet.
>> I know. Imagine when it's lit like being
satisfied already with it at its like
resting state is crazy. When it's lit
up, I would definitely cry.
>> Wow.
This is beautiful.
>> I don't know. I just feel so grateful.
>> Wow.
>> to see this
in person.
>> This is insane.
>> Wait, I don't want to get emotional. Oh,
full wow.
Like Porsha, you have no idea. I've been
dreaming of this moment.
>> Oh, baby.
>> It's just the things you see.
>> You know this is on my freaking vision
board? [laughter]
>> [crying]
>> On my vision
>> [laughter]
>> It's been on my vision board since 2019.
I was really trying to play it cool.
Like literally everyone would act like,
"You going to Paris?" I was like,
"Yeah."
>> [laughter]
>> I tried not to make it a big deal, but I
was literally freaking out in the
inside.
>> No, I have to record you. I have to
record you. [laughter] No.
>> I need I need
>> You look so You look so tiny.
>> [laughter]
>> You look so tiny.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, I can't even find you yet. Okay.
Oh my gosh. Say hi.
>> Hi.
>> Oh, you're so adorable.
>> Porsha, this is on my freaking
>> [laughter]
>> vision board.
Can you believe this?
>> Wow.
>> Oh my god.
>> No, Porsha, this is worth it. This is
worth it.
This is [music] worth it.
I can't wait to show my kids. Look at
your mommy. She's kind of She's kind of
Oh, wait.
>> I think we're supposed to watch out for
the cops.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I forgot [laughter] about that.
>> Okay guys, I'll talk to you later. I
love you from Paris.
>> Guys, I just came on here to show you
proof of life.
>> I can't believe we're up this early.
>> see? It is morning. I literally heard
hear birds chirping and we're just
coming home. This is too funny.
>> Okay, long story short, we woke up late.
Which was expected. I mean, we did come
in at like 5:00, almost 6:00 a.m.
And originally our itinerary was set to
like, you know,
I kind of planned it out
to be like very like, okay, we want to
do this, we want to do that. And me and
Flo we just both decided that we're just
going to go with the flow.
Um, just because we're tired, we want to
sleep, we want to enjoy it. We don't
want to feel like we're just like going,
going, going.
And um, [snorts] cuz today we're going
to go see the Dior exhibit and all this
other like I had like the Dior exhibit,
a couple other museums cuz I really like
art and I wanted to see all that stuff.
But we're just like, you know, we'll
just pick one and we'll go. So Flo is
sleeping right now. I'm type of person
once I'm up, I'm up. So
while she's sleeping, I'm going to wash
my hair because my hair is starting to
like
do this thing
when you know it's time to wash it. Um,
so yeah, let's go see the store and
welcome to
our first official full day in Paris.
>> Your destination is on your right.
>> Oh, yes, we're right here.
Okay guys, I think I'm going to grab
some Madeleine cookies.
They're not fresh, but
they will do.
>> [music]
>> God
I'm about to stock up on my La
Roche-Posay
Cicaplast cream.
It's so much cheaper here.
>> For someone who never cooks, this is
very odd.
Is Paris perhaps changing [music]
princess?
>> [music]
>> Look who came to join us. Say hi to
Tifola.
>> Hi.
>> Got to eat your fiber, Z.
We have our little friends for the day.
I'll show you the outfits later. We're
trying to record a
somewhat of an outfit of the day video
or something.
>> [singing]
[laughter]
[singing]
>> Guys, we are on the way to explore
[music] in Paris at 5:00 p.m. but you
know, your faves.
We look
so good. We look so chic.
I love it here. I love Paris.
>> What is that?
>> Okay, we're going to make some TikToks
so make sure you're follow me on Tik Tok
so you don't ever miss the vibes.
I don't know. Just search it. We're
trying to find sounds to me.
>> [music]
>> Oh, look. It's the Arc de Triomphe. Can
you believe it took 30 [music] years to
finish building?
Oh, yes. The Eiffel Tower, one of the
world's most [music] famous landmark.
Seems like we'll be seeing it quite
often.
>> Camera move, okay.
Are you happy to be in Paris?
Okay, can we move up some?
You can see it more.
It's so big, it doesn't even fit in this
frame.
Ah, the Eiffel Tower.
>> [laughter]
>> Do your thing, baby.
I love your outfit today. It's adorable.
We did burpees [music] only on an ice
but like 20 minutes just trying to take
photos here.
And now our tea is cold.
Now we're drinking lukewarm lukewarm uh
hot chocolate. And that's tea, okay?
Anyhoo, um
This has been such a slow trip, but I'm
really enjoying it.
>> It's like New York.
>> It is It reminds me of New York when we
went the last time.
For sure. No one sits outside.
Like no one sits outside.
So nice.
>> [music]
>> You guys know me, I'm a problem
solutions type of girl, so
my phone cracked, we found a repair shop
that is Express. We got here like lucky
5 minutes ago, right before
and my phone is ready.
Hello.
That's what I love because I'm not going
to lie.
I was kind of a bit like, you know,
>> [snorts]
>> and as much as vacation is vacation, I'm
like responding to emails, work, all
that stuff on my phone and stuff.
I could not afford to not have my phone.
But, I want to talk about like
expectation versus reality.
One thing I love about Paris, everything
is so efficient here, like
and I like that.
But,
even like the cafes, like
when you get there, you just sit, like
you seat yourself. There's no like
hostess and stuff. That was really
interesting. Cuz my phone or whatever
was going on.
I need to brush my teeth.
Don't tell me what to do with my teeth.
>> [music]
>> The Eiffel Tower again.
I told you we would be seeing it a lot.
>> [music]
>> We are on the boat cruise.
The Eiffel Tower is sparkling, but I
can't get it in the frame anymore.
Anyhow,
>> Oh, we can. You can cut it there.
>> It's so cute when it's sparkling. So
girl a lot.
>> Hello indeed.
>> Is that the church?
It is.
It's Notre Dame.
Wow.
Wait till you see the La of Familia.
Pretty, but I wanted to show you guys
the OOTD because I finished the jacket
and the top and it's so cute. I'm not
sure about this waist belt yet. I added
it just because in the original inspo,
it was there.
But the jacket is so lovely.
And it's so well done. It's fully lined.
Like I'm so proud of how it's turned out
with the top. Snatching me real nice.
You know the vibe.
to Cafe Carrousel. It's right next to
the other cafe we went to yesterday, but
it's just one of those places we really
really wanted to go. So this time we're
going a little earlier so we can just
wait in line and get a spot. So we're
off there now and then after that we're
going to go to the museum and then
tonight we're going to the ballet. So we
want to like go to the museum and
everything so we have time to come back
and
go to the ballet. Today's a pink day. I
have on this pink outfit and then later
today I'm wearing this pink dress that I
made like almost 2 years ago for
Valentine's Day.
So I don't know. It's kind of cute like
wearing your own clothes that you've
made
in Pari. I need to spray my hair.
I guess I'm going to sing for you today.
Yes.
She [music] looks so cute. [singing]
She's so preppy, so pretty.
Okay.
I'll talk to you guys when we get to
Carrousel. I'm trying to do better at
not yapping so much on these vlogs
[music] so that way we can like show you
more of what we're doing and less of my
yapping yapping yapping.
Oh, it's so cute.
>> adorable.
I look like Dora the Explorer.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm like a mommy.
Mommy and daughter. Mommy and daughter.
You're taking a picture of us.
>> [music]
>> Honestly, it's the simple things. A cute
little cafe lunch with your friend with
the Eiffel Tower view just miles away. I
love Paris and you do too.
Cuz we're in a little bit of a hurry.
But we are on our way.
At the playhouse.
But
I lied to her. It's not good to lie to
your friends. I swear. But I like to
follow on Instagram. I said I was at
7:00 but it's really at 8:00 but it's
because You know with the ballet you
have to get there early and then
No, we got
it. We were going to be late. So I told
her it was at 7:00 so she already
thought like we were late and I was
like, "Oh, it's actually at 8:00."
But sometimes you just got to do what
you got to do. Also, whenever I heard
that news I was so relieved.
I was so happy. So, no worries.
We're so excited. We'll talk to you guys
when we get in there. I heard that this
building is like so beautiful.
I hope they let us record in there.
>> We're actually watching the ballet in
Paris.
>> my first time
>> Wow.
>> going to the ballet so
>> I'm probably going to shed a tear.
>> I will for sure.
Well, I just got to just know how it
goes. Love you. Bye.
>> [music]
>> I feel a little bit overdressed but
I mean,
maybe the kids still hang out here.
Yeah.
No, we're here.
>> [laughter]
>> Was that like I'm mad that the DJI is
not a wide angle lens?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my gosh, I might cry.
What a perfect place to watch our first
ballet.
>> I know. I'm so excited.
>> I'm so happy.
>> [laughter]
>> I will show you guys a lot more. I know
you guys are tired of seeing our You're
never tired of seeing our faces.
You're never tired of that.
>> Never that.
>> But I'll show you more of the scenery.
It's [music] just a lot of people in the
way, so I'm trying to be respectful.
>> Yeah.
>> But shout out to now.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's beautiful.
Uh
Actually
It's pretty good. Like, we're really
close to the front.
But
Sorry.
>> Yeah.
I'm just a few years before
>> [music]
>> Anyways, we're in awe.
Very much so.
If you guys like art and ballets and
stuff, comment down below and let us
know what's like your favorite like
artist or
art style.
Um favorite type of dance, you know,
let's let's get to chatting in the
comments.
Love you.
>> [music]
[music]
[applause]
>> If you're watching this vlog cuz you're
planning on coming to Paris,
if the ballet's on your itinerary, just
know that like when it's over, if you
care about pictures, I don't know if you
guys can tell, but me and Pụlô love to
take photos.
>> [laughter]
>> And we never post them.
>> Never post them.
>> You know, it's just for fun, for the
vibes. But if you're planning on coming,
right when it's over, run to the little
balcony area and grab one and stay
there. Don't don't be generous.
>> Don't leave.
>> Stay there. Stay there and take all your
cute pictures because they I feel like I
want to say maybe 10 minutes, maybe
seven, seven 10 minutes they'll like
make everyone leave.
>> Oh, yeah. And then go during
intermission.
>> Oh, yes. Yes. During intermission, go.
>> As soon as they stop, run.
>> Run, get your picture.
>> Make mommy proud.
>> Go, baby, go.
>> Run, run.
>> Are you ready?
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, we are headed to Coco for dinner.
And we will talk to you guys soon cuz I
need to look at my maps.
>> Oh, yeah, we are going.
>> Good night.
>> Ah, olala.
>> Crazy.
>> Could I go go go go go?
>> Yeah, Coco.
>> [gasps]
>> Okay, guys, we're heading in.
>> And baby girl, my lover.
>> You know when I
when I bring my man back here, I'm going
to be like I know a spot. I know a spot.
>> I'll show you something.
>> I know a spot.
>> [music and singing]
[music]
[singing]
>> It sure doesn't hurt to have something
nice to look at while you eat.
He looked good and he played good,
[music] too. Yum.
>> [laughter]
>> We already knew Princess was ordering
pasta. This girl never changes.
>> I thought I'd turn the camera off. We
both had such a lovely dinner.
>> It was so lovely.
>> Like it was so nice. We had a little
therapy session.
>> [laughter]
>> And we literally just talked for so
long. It's now like almost 1:00 a.m.
>> I know, right?
>> And then tell them where we're going.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Your favorite Guess what?
Guess what we're doing. Mind you, we
have to be up for early in the morning,
but we're going to go out.
>> Hi.
Bonsoir.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> We are ready [music]
for
the style. Let me show you my outfit.
So, I have this At first, I had on this
different outfit, but I changed because
it's just giving a bit um
young.
You know.
But now I have on this top and this
skirt. The only reason I'm wearing the
boots is because
um
it's going to be raining today. So, shut
up.
Prep my leave out. Maybe I'll take like
a little hat or something.
My whole outfit
I think
I think this top is from
>> Shein.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> Yeah.
>> This top is from Shein.
And then the white top is from Seth's
Closet.
>> [laughter and clears throat]
>> This skirt is from Fashion Nova.
And then these boots, I think it's also
from Shein. I don't know if you guys can
see it. Oh, we're kind of matching in
our color schemes.
>> Yeah.
>> I think we're always matching.
>> We're always like
>> unintentionally.
>> Yeah. Telepathy.
>> Okay, let's go. We got to get to
walking. Hopefully I'm praying God holds
the rain. Like I hope
>> Check the weather.
No, yours is cuter.
>> I don't know why I don't like it.
What was that about?
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, I guess I'll just have it on for
safekeeping.
Cuz I don't even have anything to like
redo my leave out if it it gets wet.
Okay, it's not that bad. I think I just
feel like howdy, y'all.
But not even howdy, more like
all aboard.
finger
Okay, actually yeah, put your hat on.
Let's match.
>> This This one is kind of ghetto
>> [laughter]
>> compared to yours.
>> So I think I don't even know if I can
fit in my bag.
And this is our girl breakfast. We're so
we eat like birds.
>> It's cute.
>> No, it looks good on the camera, but in
real life How does this look?
>> It's like [laughter] deeper.
>> This camera is discriminating us.
I think
>> [laughter]
>> But you like the rain won't do too much
to you though. So I don't think you have
to wear
but it's cute.
>> Unless you cuz I can't redo that.
I'm not bad. Hopefully guys, we made it
to the train station. It's very
interesting here. It's a bit um
confusing.
But I feel like we'll figure it out.
We're taking the Rex C.
Just following the instructions I got
online
from our favorite chat Tippy Tay.
But we'll see you soon. Ciao.
>> [music]
>> Versailles is technically not in
It is about 30 to 40 minutes out [music]
by train. So, we hopped on the train on
LAX with a dream in our cardigan.
>> [laughter]
>> And we headed [music] to Versailles.
Riding the train was not complicated at
all. As I'm someone who travels or has
been traveling [music] to European
cities, I've noticed that a lot of their
train systems are almost identical. So,
we just followed our maps and it brought
[music] us to Versailles.
Hold on, it's raining. Perhaps I should
have put on
some pants and not this
tiny little Asian Doll skirt. Y'all, I'm
cold. I feel like I'm going to catch a
cold. Guys, it's the way we literally
called an Uber for a 5-minute walk.
It's so
>> [laughter]
>> It's so cold. And what's even funnier,
>> [snorts]
>> I was going to wear this big brown
trench and we're like, "Nah, it's It's
covering the outfit."
>> [gasps]
>> And follow, she's going to wear the big
black jacket. Like, why did we do this?
Um I think that's it.
Wow.
Guys, we're here.
I can't wait to go inside.
>> [music]
>> Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
Versailles.
If you're not sure why Versailles is
important or have never heard of it,
Versailles is just this massive royal
palace located in the town of
Versailles. It is famous for just being
gaudy and large and beautiful. There's
so much intricate
>> [music]
>> art and just so much beauty in this one
place. It was actually where [music]
Louis the VIII lived and Marie
Antoinette lived here as well. [music]
It is known for the Hall of Mirrors,
which is just like this really long
room, which we'll be entering [music] in
just a little bit. It is absolutely
stunning, and I feel like if you are in
Paris, you absolutely must visit
Versailles. Yes, it is a little bit of a
line to get in, and yes, it is [music]
people. I mean, it's a tourist
attraction. There's always going to be
people here, but there's just something
about being in places like this that
just fills me as an artist and as a
person to just see what the humans
before [music] us were able to create
before electricity. And it just I
my mind is just blown, and it just
reminds me that we all have such
infinite possibilities of what we can
create within us, and I just hope that
we are able to all maximize our
potential here on Earth. That is what
Versailles means to me. It is gaudy.
It's a castle, and as a princess myself,
I'm glad to be here.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Imagine I'm going to sleep over here.
Like, hey guys, this is my room.
Huge stairs. Like, I want my house like
this.
Like, imagine you're coming home from
dinner, you're like,
Do you need an elevator?
>> I hurt my heels.
>> Oh, guys, look.
Isn't this so real?
Les Grands Appartements. Bonsoir.
Today, I don't even know.
You guys know
I always like to travel with braids
because I just don't like to deal with
hot tools and all that stuff. So, I'm
kind of proud of myself, but honestly,
it's really not that hard. It's a middle
part. There's no edges.
I just [snorts] have to like comb it, so
I'm kind of loving this.
We are on the way to the Louvre.
Um I have on Wait, let me see how far
back I can go. Maybe you guys I don't
know if you guys can see that.
I have on this top from H&M. I don't
know if you guys can tell, but right
before this trip, literally the day
before, I went to H&M and I bought a
whole bunch of stuff.
Cuz I was like, "I don't have anything
to wear." So.
This top is from H&M. The capri pants
are from H&M as well. And then I have
these um
pointed toe shoes.
>> I don't want to say something stupid.
Hey guys.
>> Cuckoo.
Check out my outfit.
>> Very cute version. [music]
I have a very cute slick white
asymmetrical top. [music] Honestly, I
wanted to try the asymmetrical
and see how it looks.
>> Asymmetrical what?
>> Tops. I love asymmetrical tops. They're
so cute.
>> It's just
>> [music]
>> elevate an outfit.
And then I think I got this top on
Amazon cuz I was also doing last minute
shopping. Guys, we literally booked this
trip like
a week ago.
>> Yeah.
>> So.
Got this from Amazon. This skirt, I
believe I got this from
Shein or Fashion Nova.
And then this jacket,
>> [music]
>> this lovely
spiky jacket is from Saks Fifth Avenue.
>> From Revolve. It's such a good jacket,
y'all.
>> Yeah.
See my sister's hat from Amazon.
>> Yeah, I got that from Amazon.
But yeah, I think we are looking very
>> chic.
>> Very chic.
>> I'll tell them where where Oh, we're not
going to the Louvre yet. Guys, I'm so
sorry. I lied.
>> [music]
>> Oh yeah, we're going to the
>> The Louvre is at Our tickets for the
Louvre is at 7:00.
>> Mhm.
>> Right now it's like 5:00 something and
we're trying to see if we can make it to
the Dior exhibit because we couldn't go
on Monday.
>> Cuz we're believers.
>> We're delusional.
>> Mhm.
Ciao for now.
Mwah.
Honestly, I think I just came [music]
back to show you guys the glasses
because I feel like we've elevated the
look.
Okay, yeah. We decided to go out. I'm
not even a sunglasses person [music]
because sometimes I'm just like how do
people wear this all day?
I can barely see. You know everything is
all good.
But we survive, you know, it's chic.
Put the glasses on. Let's act like we
walk out. We're like
move, silence.
Silence first.
Give me my coffee.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So we came to the art exhibit, but guess
what? It's closed. Chad C when I catch
you, Ricky.
>> [laughter]
>> I know you guys probably think we're
like the most unserious girls in the
world.
But you know, we just live a
high V vibe sometimes. All right.
What is this heaven? Like this was such
a waste of a 30 minute Uber.
Okay. You're lucky that they're right
next to this The Champs.
So we can just do a little shopping
around.
A little looking around. Yeah. Okay. We
will chat to you guys later.
>> I have to say, I love to see these
[music] two indulge in luxury.
Hey, work hard. They deserve a little
treat.
Happy shopping, [music] ladies.
Yes, Paula Celine [music] is your
runway. Work it.
>> This is really nice piece.
>> Let me see it.
Yeah, it's really cute.
>> fabulous.
Oh my god, I love this.
And you can
>> It looks really good on you.
>> Like you have like a perfect
>> It looks I even think it fits your
outfit right now.
>> It does.
>> Just holding it.
>> You you can put the chain into the bag.
Mhm.
Yes.
>> Okay.
>> What am I doing?
>> I love this so much.
>> Mhm.
>> Just like this.
>> Oh, it's so cute.
>> [laughter]
>> Add it to your birthday list.
>> Birthday gift? [music]
>> Birthday gift.
Yes. Guys, look at my baby.
She's so adorable.
It's like
I never really [music] cared about the
bag until now that you showed it.
This bag is insane. I literally saw it
in the window and I was like, you can
have to come home with me.
So guys, make sure [music] you like,
comment, subscribe, share this video
with your friends. This bag got a paper
cut.
This bag got a paper cut. So, okay,
honey. Thanks for watching.
>> She's so good at everything.
>> And she can style it up however she
wants to. She can wear literally a
two-piece casual set and fashion is in
the bag.
>> [laughter]
>> And she's chic. She's chic.
>> Simple. Very.
>> Running on a high of owning my very
[music] first pair of Goyard bag. We're
on the way to the Louvre because how can
you [music] come to Paris and not go to
the Louvre?
Say with me everybody, the Louvre.
>> Hi guys. I found a hat. I had to protect
the leave-out.
>> Oh my god.
>> Anyways, we are at the Louvre.
Funny enough, I did not imagine that it
would be inside what seems to be a mall.
I don't know what I thought it would The
entrance would be like.
But, it's just not this. You know, I
feel like a lot of vlogs I've seen,
people don't show getting there. They
just show themselves when they're there.
But, just know
Oh my god.
We're Oh my god. Okay, we got to go.
There's a lot going on. I'll talk to you
guys later.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Guys, I'm quite enjoying the Louvre at
night.
Yeah. It seems calmer.
It's not as crowded. It's not as
crowded.
Wow.
Bonjour.
I think it's kind of dark. But, we're
leaving now. The Louvre closed.
Yeah, we'll talk later.
>> Hi. Hi.
>> We're done at the Louvre. Mhm.
But, it was really lovely. I really
liked it.
It's very grandiose, very beautiful.
Very, you know, everything you would
expect from a like the most famous
museum in the world.
Wait, Fola, what did you say?
Okay.
Guys, it's me again. I had to commit to
the glasses because
it messed up the makeup on my nose. But,
we're waiting on our Uber right now.
We're going to dinner at a place called
Kalamata.
At first, we were going to change um to
just more like dresses because this is
very like chic.
But,
we um we're just really hungry, you
know?
And the outfits which we can wear it
somewhere else. But, Fola is going to
find some
souvenirs for her sisters.
GW, okay. I think my Uber is here.
No, yeah. Okay, I'll just sit right here
and wait on her.
But,
I hope you guys are enjoying the vlog.
I feel like I've not been vlogging as
much or maybe that's just me being in my
head. But, I really hope that you guys
are just loving this. I'm really trying
to make you feel like you're here
because
with the vlogs it's always like we're
here together, we're experiencing it
together.
Um with the Louvre, we honestly only
spent about I want to say maybe 2 hours
in here. And a lot of it was just us
like making jokes and like talking,
making videos. And I didn't really
record too much of the inside. Like we
barely even scratched the surface
of what's in here. So this is definitely
a place to where I feel like it's kind
of like the Met in New York. You can
come often and like see new things,
maybe learn the history of a piece, come
back and see it. There was a guy in
there who was explaining the one big
painting of Jesus
where it's like Jesus and he's like in
the synagogue with all of these people
and like he was explaining it.
And it was just such a beautiful
interpretation of it and I was like,
"Wow,
that really is what art is. It's just
like what you see."
So it was really nice. I really liked
it.
Um
yeah, I'm feeling very grateful. Me and
Paula like
today has been such a good day. Minus
the fact that we have not eaten. Oop.
Well, we ate like here and there, like
little snacks, but we have not eaten a
real full hearty meal today just cuz
we've been on the go.
It kind of occurred to us that this is
technically our last day. I thought
Saturday was going to be our last day
cuz we're going somewhere else and we're
coming back.
Um
>> [clears throat]
>> but I read the the flight details wrong
and we're actually going to be coming
back to Paris around like 7:00 p.m. So
you know,
we're just trying now to see what we
can, do what we can, check off
everything on our list. Not because we
won't be back, but just because you
know, it's our first time. We want to
like do all these exciting things.
But yeah, it's been such a great day.
I'm so happy.
Um I love my bag that I bought. I can't
wait to go home and like do an unboxing
for my friends. Yeah, I'm so happy and I
pray that this vlog reaches all the
right audiences and I pray that as
you're watching this in this moment, why
am I getting emotional? As you're
watching this in this moment, I just
pray over you and I speak
just joy into your lives. I just pray
that cuz for me Paris is is technically
a dream and I put it on quotation marks
because it's just one of those things
where it's like, you know, I assume
everyone wants to, you know, visit
Paris. Like everyone wants to come here
at least at some point. Even my college
dorm theme was Paris, you know?
So, it didn't even occur to me that this
was on my vision board like for a long
time. But to me it was just the idea of
Paris, like the idea of traveling. And
if I So, now I'm like traveling a lot.
It's like, wow, I'm really living an
answered prayer. Like I'm really And
this is so casual.
And it's not even cuz like I'm rich or
nothing. It's just
I'm just blessed like this stage of life
that I am in right now. I'm blessed. Um
I don't have kids.
I don't have really a lot of
responsibilities. My business, I've
automated it to where it kind of runs
itself now.
Um I have like a great team. Sudara, my
assistant, like they're holding down the
fort while I'm here. And it's just
lovely.
It's really nice. Um
so, yeah, like if you're currently
putting a country on your vision board
right now or there's somewhere in your
heart you've always wanted to visit, I
want you to just believe and like
know that you can absolutely get there.
And when you get there, it's not even
going to feel like, oh my gosh. It's
going to feel like, wow, this is a real
mantra.
It's going to feel like, oh, wow. You
know, like me and Phil like kept saying
like we're not going to deep that we are
in Paris until we leave and like look
back on the memories.
But
it's crazy when you when
Oh my god, what are the words? When
an answered prayer is answered, it feels
like, oh, this was always a part of the
story. Like this just feels like, oh,
yeah, this was the time I was supposed
to come here.
And it it's it's unreal, you know what
I'm saying?
Um yeah, okay. I think I've yapped and
blabbed enough.
Au revoir.
Come back. Y'all know when I'm by
myself, I get to talking.
Okay, our Uber is here. I will talk to
you later. Ciao, my love.
>> [music]
>> And then we're coming back to Paris. So,
this is a little intermission trip.
We are going to Barcelona.
Guys, Barcelona is such a special city
to me.
It's the first place I ever solo
traveled to, and it's literally like
a dream. Like, I love Barcelona. I
always would say like, "Oh, I can't wait
to go back."
>> Look at the Arc de Triomphe.
Arc de Triomphe
>> It's so cute.
>> It's so big.
Y'all, I swear
I am not under the influence. I do not
I am just filled with so much joy right
now.
The Arc de Triomphe Oh, we do have to
go. Paris, I love you. I love
>> We love you, Paris. We love you so much.
>> They're going to think we're drunk.
We're not, guys. We're We're just so
happy.
>> a good time.
>> I'm so sad.
Okay. Okay, where are we going? We've
got to cross the street that way. Okay.
>> I love you,
>> No, right now it's really fun.
>> No, we had a good time. We didn't want
to leave.
>> Yeah.
>> Why?
>> We have a flight to catch.
>> It's so crazy to say.
>> Go have fun for us.
>> Have fun, GUYS.
>> AU REVOIR.
THAT'S SO FUNNY to say. Oh, yeah, we
have a flight to catch.
>> We have a flight to catch.
>> We're not serious people.
>> We're so unserious. Our flight is IN 2
HOURS.
>> AND THEN I KEPT LOOKING AT THE TIME
LIKE,
"LIKE, 5 more minutes."
>> We kept looking at the time like,
"We We can push it." [laughter]
>> Oh my god.
>> I hope there's not a line at TSA. That'd
be very awkward.
>> We just have to beg and cry at this
point. We're going to make our flight.
>> Please, please don't cry. I have to go
home.
I have a wedding.
Please.
>> Shout out to
You
Oh my god, Puala, I fell in the water.
I fell IN THE WATER.
MY FEET IS SO COLD. OH MY GOD.
[laughter]
MY FEET IS SO COLD.
>> It's so cold.
>> Okay.
Imagine this in the summer.
>> Oh, so fun. That would be a blast.
>> We are so fun here already.
So, we're definitely coming back.
>> Yes, but we can't just be biased.
>> Wait, yes we can.
>> No, we need to check out other places.
>> Okay, guys. Puala and I
for the summer
we said we're going to do Portugal.
And then we'll go back to the south of
France cuz you know, that's our that's
our spot.
>> But I think we're going to add Paris to
the list. Puala.
This girl is just walking. Car is coming
by.
We have A FLIGHT TO CATCH.
OKAY, is it this way or that way?
>> This is the way.
>> Okay, okay.
>> We're almost there. It's 2 minutes away.
>> Okay.
Wow. [laughter]
I can't believe we're actually making
it.
>> I know.
>> [crying]
>> This is crazy.
>> I'm going to sleep so good on this
flight.
>> I know.
>> Oh, I'm going to be so sad.
You know, my mom asked when I was coming
back. I was like
>> Never.
>> Really?
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, just kidding. Monday.
>> I always said that to everyone that
asked me.
Okay.
>> Oh, to be young.
>> I'm going to say our favorite moment
again.
>> Okay, wait, wait, wait.
>> Okay.
So, my favorite moment was going to the
Versailles Palace
>> Mhm.
>> because I just feel like that's
something that
it's like when you learn about it in
history class, it feels so out of touch.
So, to actually be there was really
cool.
>> Yeah.
>> And to see how big it was was really
cool.
And then
I think seeing the Eiffel Tower the
first night.
>> [music]
>> Like that was so random.
>> That was
>> And that was really lovely.
>> That was like one of my favorite
moments, like
>> a very good moment.
>> nobody there but that one man who was
going on a run. It was just us.
>> It was just us and the big Eiffel Tower.
>> Oh my god.
>> [laughter]
>> Nigeria.
>> Yes.
>> Yes, welcome to the Paris.
>> Thank you.
>> Nice Paris, you know.
>> I love Paris.
>> I love you.
>> How many time you stay here?
>> Thank you.
I need to go back to class. I need to go
back to class.
My
My French teacher sent me my homework. I
was like, "Sorry, I'M IN PARIS."
NO WAY.
NO. GUYS, I HAVEN'T done my French
HOMEWORK IN
>> OH MY GOSH, you're skipping class.
>> in like 4 days.
>> You're skipping class.
>> I skipped class twice to be here. But I
want her to know I'm getting real life
experience. Don't play.
>> My favorite moment was also the Eiffel
Tower cuz like honestly forgot about
that.
>> really fun.
>> was such an intimate moment. Just us
with the Eiffel Tower, no one there.
>> Yeah.
>> And we actually we actually got to enjoy
seeing it full and taking it in.
>> Yeah.
>> And taking it in.
Merci.
Okay, now you're about to see like the
craziest transition of all time.
I'm going to be asleep.
I swear to you.
>> [clears throat]
>> My
>> [laughter]
>> My butt touches that.
>> You know, that's how it was um the
flight here.
>> Yeah.
>> Because the seats we had were at the
very front. It was so much space. I
literally
>> I saw you were knocked out.
>> flat out across all three seats. That
was amazing.
>> You make yourself at home.
>> Oh yeah, baby.
Okay,
>> [laughter]
>> over baby.
>> Like 10 minutes.
>> 10 minutes.
Well, we have to go. I'm going to call
the Uber when we're upstairs. So you
have to come down.
>> 5 minutes.
>> You can just get in the car. I just need
to
We need to leave by 5.
>> What time is it now?
>> 4:46.
>> Oh, we need to leave.
>> Yeah.
>> Quick.
I need to get my tax refund for my bag.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> See y'all later.
Mwah. Ciao. See you
>> At the airport.
>> Gosh, I didn't want it to end.
Oh, how amazing it is to watch a dream
[music] come true.
>> Oh, trust me. I didn't want it to end
either.
Paris is such [music] a dream, which is
why I cannot wait to go back. Which is a
lot sooner than you think. See you then.
Au revoir.
Like personally, you have no idea. I've
been dreaming of this moment.
>> Oh, baby.
>> [laughter]
>> It's been on my vision board since 2019.